jungleerummy.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - JungleeRummy.com

We respect your privacy protect it at all costs. Along with providing the most enjoyable online rummy gaming environment, we also build a relationship of trust with our members and users. We are fully committed to protecting your personal information, and this is why we are known as the most trusted multiplayer gaming website for playing rummy games on.

Our privacy policy explains in detail what information we collect, how we use that and the kinds of privacy options that are readily available to our users and members. We always ensure that whatever information you share with us remains completely protected and confidential so that you can enjoy safe online games of rummy without worrying about anything. 

## **Your Information is Safe: We Respect and Protect Your Privacy**

We provide a completely safe gaming environment on Junglee Rummy.com. We do not share or reveal your personal information to any other parties without your consent. The only information that can be shared is mentioned in the privacy policy, or in rare cases, we may need to share information when necessitated by the law. We continually strive to make a better and safer virtual environment for online gaming. In order to serve you better, we may utilize your information to inform you about our latest offers, products, contests, and prizes. When you win contests on Junglee Rummy, your information may be shared with the prize sponsors and suppliers through our site. 

## **User Information: What We Collect**

You need to register with JungleeRummy.com to enjoy 24x7 rummy games. When you register with us, we collect essential information like your unique username and email address. After you have provided this information, we also collect your IP address to analyse rummy gaming and demographic trends, to track player movement as well as for site administration. You may note that IP addresses do not anyhow contain a user’s personal identifying information. It is our own solemn policy that we do not at all sell, share or rent your vital information to any other parties in any way different from those that have been mentioned in our Privacy Policy.

## **Advanced Security for Data Protection**

We make sure that all of your information is completely secure with us. We are equipped with advanced security facilities to protect your information against unauthorized access, loss, misuse, and alteration. We also perform regular checks and reviews of our data storage facilities and constantly improve our security measures to ensure that your information is not misused. Only you can access your account, as your registration information is fully password-protected. After you have accessed your account, JungleeRummy.com is not responsible for any activity in your account, as you are the only person who can log in to your account as it requires entering your own security password. Therefore, we give you the simplest security tip: Do not disclose your password to anyone whosoever. 

## **Cookies: Accept, Modify or Decline**

When you play rummy games on our website, there is a possibility that there are some traces of our cookies on your computer. Technically, cookies are small harmless files that recognise your browser and follow up with advertisements. They can also be used for other purposes like security, authentication and the management of the online rummy game environment but they can never be used to access any information on your computer.

The advertisers on JungleeRummy.com may use cookies, as they are utilized under the scope of advertisement. Under such cases, they are not controlled by us and are only managed by the advertisers. In most of the popular browsers, cookies are usually accepted automatically. However, you can modify or decline them to prevent advertisers from displaying any advertisements. 

## **Our Policy Works with Your Consent**

It is evident that when you play our multiplayer rummy games, you play them with your full conscience and consent. As you log in, it is clearly understood that you have given your full permission to JungleeRummy.com and its partners and affiliates to collect and use your information, which you have provided. For your convenience, we believe in improving our privacy policies for better modes of collecting information. Whenever we amend any rule or policy, it will be updated on JungleeRummy.com immediately so that you are always informed about what information we collect, how it is used, and the parameters under which it is disclosed. 

JungleeRummy.com declares that this Privacy Policy is a clear explanation of the way we use your information. We are GDPR-compliant. We do not share any of your personal data with any European companies, nor do we offer our products or services to European residents. Your data is secure, protected and only available to you. We do not and will not share any of your data with any outside entity, company or individual. You will always have the option to review, update, restrict and delete your data. The policy is not intended to be used for creating any legal conflicts or rights in favour of any person. We also reserve the right to modify and implement any changes at any time without any prior notice.

Click _here_ to know our Terms of Service.
